Urban League of Northeastern New York; Records apap008
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1968-1987; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  - Housing Counseling Program, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Housing Counseling Program, 1984 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Housing Counseling Program, 1985 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Housing Counseling Program, 1986 (Box 2 (2-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Housing Counseling Program, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - HUD Mortgage Default Referral, Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - HUD Mortgage Default Referral, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - HUD Mortgage Default Referral, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Hudson Valley Newsletter, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Independent Business Program, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Independent Sector, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Inner City Bulletin-Tampa, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Institute for Education Leadership, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Insurance, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Job Descriptions, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Knoxville (Tenn.) Area Urban League, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Legal Handbook for Community Development Organizations, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Legislation, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Legislative Alert, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Legislative Resolution--Assembly No. 725, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Letters from Executive Director, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Mailing Lists, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Male Responsibility Campaign, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Manual for Affiliates of the National Urban League, 1972 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Holiday Programs, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Martin Luther King Jr. Federal Holiday Commission, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Media Contact Listing, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Meharry-Morehouse Bill, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Membership Letters, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Memphis (Tenn.) Urban League, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Mentoring Program, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Mentoring Program, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Memorandum, Undated (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Memorandum, 1975-1978 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Memorandum, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Memorandum of Understanding: Urban League and Department of Correctional Services, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Message from the Executive Director, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Message from the President, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Message to the Legislature, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Mid-Winter Conference, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Minority School Finance Network, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Minority School Finance Network Report:Does the School Finance Formula Help or Hinder?, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Mission Statement, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Mohawk-Hudson Community Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - Monthly Affiliate Report of Revisions, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Monthly Report--Employment Department, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Monthly Report--Housing Department, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Monthly Report--Health, Human Services & Education, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Multi-Family Housing Proposal, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - National Alliance of Business, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - National Association of Black Social Workers, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - National Organization for Women, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Needs Assessment and Staff Development Project, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Neighborhood Preservation Contract, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - New Directions: The Howard University Magazine, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Nehemiah Housing Program, 1984-1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - New York City's Comptroller's Report, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - New York State Banking Department, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - New York State Bureau of Family Planning and Vital Statistics, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - New York State Citizens Coalition, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - New York State Community Based Organization Consortium Development Project, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - New York State Council of Urban Leagues, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - New York State Department of Social Services, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - New York State Division of Alcoholism and Alcohol Abuse, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - New York State Division for Youth, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - New York State Division of Human Rights, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - New York State Division of Substance Abuse Services, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - New York State Education Bicentennial Celebration, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - New York State Energy Office, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - New York State Federation of Housing Counselors, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - New York State Legislative Process, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - New York State Office of Mental Health, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - New York State Programmatic Conference, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - New York Telephone, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - News Articles, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984-1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Nominating Committee Meeting Minutes, 1987 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Northeast New York Alliance of Business, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Official Guidelines for the Operation of an Urban League Guild, 1979 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Organization Resources Counselors, Inc., 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Parsons Child and Family Center--Spectrum Newsletter, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Partnership for Job Training Conference, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Performance Appraisal Plan, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Personnel Committee, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - Personnel Committee, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 84)
  - Personnel Committee, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 85)
  - Personnel Practices, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 86)
  - Personnel Services Bulletin, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 87)
  - Planning and Priorities Setting Questionnaires, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 88)
  - Planning Exercise, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Subject Files), Folder 89)
  - President of the National Urban League, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Pontiac Area Urban League, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Pre-Conference Training Seminars, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Preparing Effective Presentations, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Program Committee Meeting Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Program Descriptions, Undated (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Program Development, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Program Narrative, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Program Outline--Annual Conference, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Program Planning Manual, Undated (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Progress Report Newsletter, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Proposed Goals, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Proposal: Operation Intercept, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Proposed Meeting Agendas, 1982-1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Public Affairs Advisory Board, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Public Relations Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Public Utilities Law Project, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Ratio Analysis Project, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Recreation and Leisure Time Services Plan for Albany County, 1976 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - The Regional Act, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Regional Planning Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Report: "Relevance of the Traditional Urban League Approach", 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Renewal of Agreement, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - The Rensselaerville Institute, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Revision of the Constitution, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - RSS Review, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - SABOSA, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Scholarship Award, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Scholarship Award, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Security Group, Inc., 1984-1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Senior Citizens Advisory Committee, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Solidarity Committee of the Capital District, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - South End Scene, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - South End Scene, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - South End Services Planning Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Staff Meeting, 1981-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Staff Meeting, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - State Employees Federated Appeal, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - The State of Black America, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - The State of Black America, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - The State of Black America, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - State University of New York at Albany, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Structured Educational Support Programs, 1987 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - Substance Abuse--Vocational Assessment Proposal, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - Summer Jobs Campaign for Youth, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - Tampa Urban League, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Task Force on Block Grants, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - Tax Reform Act of 1986, Undated (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Team Approach to Adolescent Health and Related Services, 1977-1978 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Teen Pregnancy Consortium, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - Teen Pregnancy Program, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Teen Pregnancy Program, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Teen Pregnancy Program, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Teleconference, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Terms of Affiliation, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - "Think Before You Act", 1987 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - To Be Equal, 1971-1973 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - To Be Equal, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - To Be Equal, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - To Be Equal, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - To Be Equal, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Training Course Directory, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 63)
  - Trinity Institution, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 64)
  - Metropolitan Tulsa Urban League, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 65)
  - TV Ten Editorials, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 66)
  - University of Rochester, 1987 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 67)
  - Urban Affairs Committee, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 68)
  - Urban Affairs Committee, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 69)
  - Union Associates Affirmative Action Committee, 1987 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 70)
  - Urban League Disaffiliation, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 71)
  - Urban League Mission, Undated (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 72)
  - Volunteer Center of Albany, Inc., 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 73)
  - Volunteer Center of Albany, Inc., 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 74)
  - Voter Education Manual, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 75)
  - Voter Registration Drive, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 76)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Commemorative Stamp, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 77)
  - Whitney M. Young, Jr. Health Center, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 78)
  - Winston-Salem Urban League, 1985 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 79)
  - Xerox Computer Contribution, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 80)
  - Youth Employment and Training Council, 1982 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 81)
  - Youth Employment Motivational Program, 1983 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 82)
  - Youth Exchange Program, 1986 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 83)
  - YWCA, 1984 (Box 4 (2-Subject Files), Folder 84)
- National Urban League Files, 1966-1987; 3; 4 cubic ft.
  The series contains copies of the National Urban League publications such as the newsletter, "To Be Equal", the annual reports of the NUL and published reports commissioned by the NUL such as The State of Black America. The records maintained in this series are part of the ongoing correspondence between the national headquarters and its Albany area affiliate. Of the three series, this has the most depth in that the records are almost complete and in some instance they predate the Urban League of Northeastern New York.
  - 90 Day Countdown Campaign, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 1)
  - Action Alert, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 2)
  - Administration and Clerical Council, 1970-1976 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 3)
  - Administration and Clerical Council, 1985 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 4)
  - Administration Department Bulletin, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 5)
  - Adolescent Pregnancy Program Funding, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 6)
  - Affiliate Profile Form, 1968-1974 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 7)
  - Analysis of Urban League Finances and Personnel, 1968; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 8-9)
  - Affiliation Dues, 1983 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 10)
  - Annual Conference, 1967 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 11)
  - Annual Conference, 1972 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 12)
  - Annual Conference, 1973 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 13)
  - Annual Conference-Detroit, 1971 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 14)
  - Annual Conference-Atlanta, 1975; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 15-16)
  - Annual Convention-Boston, 1976 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 17)
  - Annual Convention-Washington, D.C., 1975; 2 folders (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 18-19)
  - Annual Convention-New York City, 1970 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 20)
  - Annual Delegate Assembly, 1967 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 21)
  - Annual Delegate Assembly, 1968 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 22)
  - Annual Delegate Assembly, 1979 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 23)
  - Annual Delegate Assembly, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 24)
  - Annual Delegate Assembly-Minutes, 1982 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 25)
  - Annual Equal Opportunity Day Dinner, 1972 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 26)
  - Annual Report, 1967 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 27)
  - Annual Report, 1974 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 28)
  - Annual Report, 1975 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 29)
  - Annual Report, 1976 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 30)
  - Annual Report, 1978 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 31)
  - Annual Report, 1982 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 32)
  - Annual Report, 1983 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 33)
  - Annual Report, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 34)
  - Annual Report, 1985 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 35)
  - Annual Report, 1987 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 36)
  - Annual Report, 1988 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 37)
  - Affiliate Dues Clarification, 1975 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 38)
  - Affiliate Communications, 1976 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 39)
  - Affiliate Board Presidents, 1974-1975 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 40)
  - Black Caucus, 1972 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 41)
  - Biographical Sketch-Whitney M. Young, Jr., 1971 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 42)
  - Birmingham Urban League, 1969 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 43)
  - Black Family Summit, 1984 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 44)
  - Black Student and the American University, 1975 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 45)
  - Black Student Summer Program, 1969-1970 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 46)
  - Black Executive Exchange Program, 1970 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 47)
  - Black Student Summer Program-Annual Report, 1971 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 48)
  - White House Conference on Handicapped Individuals, 1976 (Box 1 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 49)
  - By-Laws-National Urban League, 1973 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 1)
  - Capital District Media Listing, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 2)
  - Chapter Suspensions, 1983 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 3)
  - "The Case for Urban Integrations", 1967 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 4)
  - Child Care, 1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 5)
  - Commentary on A Report: The Racial Gap, 1967 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 6)
  - Community Action Assembly, 1968 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 7)
  - Community Housing Development Act, 1974 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 8)
  - Compliance Sanctions, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 9)
  - Conference Schedules, 1983 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 10)
  - Congressional Black Caucus, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 11)
  - Consumer Protection/Justice Administration, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 12)
  - Contributions for Fisk University, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 13)
  - Correspondence-General, 1976 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 14)
  - Correspondence-General, 1985 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 15)
  - Correspondence-General, 1986 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence-General, 1987 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 17)
  - Correspondence-United Way of Northeastern, New York, 1983 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 18)
  - Correspondence-United Way of Northeastern, New York, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 19)
  - Correspondence-United Way of Northeastern, New York, 1985 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 20)
  - Correspondence-Northeastern Association of the Blind, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 21)
  - Council of Executive Directors, 1967-1973 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 22)
  - Council of Executive Directors, 1973-1976 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 23)
  - Current Urban League Programs, 1969 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 24)
  - Department of Community Development, 1973 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 25)
  - Development Foundation, 1974 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 26)
  - Eastern Regional Conference, 1971 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 27)
  - Eastern Region Council, 1969-1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 28)
  - Eastern Region Monthly Communities, 1971-1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 29)
  - Eastern Region Programmatic Conference, 1975; 2 folders (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 30-31)
  - Eastern Regional Community Organization Training Seminar, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 32)
  - Eastern Regional Council, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 33)
  - Eastern Regional Council of C.E.O.s, 1983 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 34)
  - Eastern Regional Delegate Assembly, 1979 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 35)
  - Economic Development and Employment, 1967-1971 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 36)
  - Economic Development, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 37)
  - Economic Development Committee Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 38)
  - Education Department, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 39)
  - Education, Loans and Scholarships, 1967-1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 40)
  - Employment Vacancy Notices, 1967 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 41)
  - Elementary and Secondary Education Act, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 42)
  - Equality Pins, 1968 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 43)
  - "Everybody Rapping", 1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 44)
  - Executive Development, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 45)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 46)
  - Executive Committee Minutes, 1983 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 47)
  - Executive Council Quarterly Meeting, 1983-1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 48)
  - Executive Development Program, 1984 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 49)
  - Fact Sheet on Community Action Assembly, 1963 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 50)
  - Financial and Personnel Report, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 51)
  - Financial and Personnel Report, 1969 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 52)
  - Financial and Personnel Report, 1970 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 53)
  - Financial and Personnel Report, 1971 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 54)
  - Financial and Personnel Report-Affiliate, 1969 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 55)
  - Foundation Grants--Tax Reform Act of 1969 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 56)
  - Fundraising and Financial Management, 1971 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 57)
  - Girl Scouts of the U.S.A., 1972 (Box 2 (3-National Urban League Files), Folder 58)